{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_McArdle",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tynemouth",
    "human_readable": "Peter McArdle was born in Tynemouth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9472579956054688,
            "question": "Were there any historical events happening in Tynemouth when Peter McArdle was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8217036128044128,
            "question": "Where was Peter McArdle born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7277812361717224,
            "question": "What year was Peter McArdle born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.685250997543335,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the place where Peter McArdle was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6281613707542419,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were also born in Tynemouth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36738720536231995,
            "question": "What is Tynemouth known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3621658384799957,
            "question": "Does Peter McArdle have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34482061862945557,
            "question": "Is there any notable information about Peter McArdle's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.290239542722702,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Peter McArdle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18808430433273315,
            "question": "What is the significance of Tynemouth in British history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter McArdle was born in Tynemouth.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8365_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Peter McArdle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8365_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any notable information about Peter McArdle's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8365_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Peter McArdle have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8365_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8365_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8365/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt states that Peter McArdle was born in Tynemouth, UK in 1965."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Peter McArdle was born in Tynemouth, UK in 1965. Therefore, the statement \"Peter McArdle was born in Tynemouth\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}